{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20smallest%20unit%20of%20matter%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Atom",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Molecule",
        "Cell",
        "Proton"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20element%20is%20represented%20by%20the%20chemical%20symbol%20'H'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Hydrogen",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Helium",
        "Hassium",
        "Hafnium"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20pH%20scale%20used%20to%20measure%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Acidity%20or%20Alkalinity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Temperature",
        "Pressure",
        "Volume"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20do%20you%20call%20substances%20that%20cannot%20be%20broken%20down%20by%20chemical%20means%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Element",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Compound",
        "Mixture",
        "Solution"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20chemical%20symbol%20for%20gold%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Au",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Go",
        "Ag",
        "Gl"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20gas%20is%20most%20abundant%20in%20Earth's%20atmosphere%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Nitrogen",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Oxygen",
        "Carbon%20Dioxide",
        "Argon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20chemical%20symbol%20for%20iron%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Fe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ir",
        "In",
        "Io"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20process%20of%20a%20substance%20in%20a%20gaseous%20state%20transforming%20into%20a%20liquid%20state%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Condensation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Evaporation",
        "Solidification",
        "Sublimation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20subatomic%20particles%20are%20found%20in%20the%20nucleus%20of%20an%20atom%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Protons%20and%20Neutrons",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Protons%20and%20Electrons",
        "Electrons%20and%20Neutrons",
        "Neutrons%20and%20Photons"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20study%20of%20the%20composition%2C%20structure%2C%20properties%2C%20and%20reactions%20of%20matter%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Chemistry",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physics",
        "Biology",
        "Geology"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
